<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-05-07T09:44:36+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Oranges</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/07/oranges.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oranges" /><published>2025-05-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/07/oranges</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/07/oranges.html"><![CDATA[<p>Orange is the edible fruit of various citrus trees. It belongs to the Rutaceae family and is one of the most popular fruits around the world.</p>

<p>The common orange is spherical to slightly oblate in shape, usually measuring around 6–9 cm (2.4–3.5 in) in diameter. It features a bright, vibrant, textured peel that ranges from orange - yellow to deep orange in color. This peel is both fragrant and slightly bumpy, protecting the juicy segments inside. The flesh of an orange is divided into numerous wedges filled with succulent, juicy, and pulp - filled vesicles. These vesicles are filled with a sweet - tart liquid, giving the fruit its characteristic refreshing taste. The flesh is typically a rich, bright orange color, and it may contain small, edible seeds in some varieties. Oranges are known for their high vitamin C content and have a lively, zesty flavor that can be both sweet and tangy, making them a delicious and healthy snack.</p>]]></content><author><name>ted</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orange is the edible fruit of various citrus trees. It belongs to the Rutaceae family and is one of the most popular fruits around the world.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Batman</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/07/batman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Batman" /><published>2025-05-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/07/batman</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/07/batman.html"><![CDATA[<p>Batman was created by artist Bob Kane and writer Bill Finger. The character made his debut in 1939 in “Detective Comics” #27. The inspiration for Batman came from various sources, including the pulp magazine heroes of the 1930s and the myth of the bat. The most well - known origin story of Batman is that young Bruce Wayne witnessed the murder of his parents, Thomas and Martha Wayne, in an alley. This traumatic event drove him to vow to fight crime and protect the people of Gotham City.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/css/images/Batman.png" alt="Batman" /></p>]]></content><author><name>xin</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Batman was created by artist Bob Kane and writer Bill Finger. The character made his debut in 1939 in “Detective Comics” #27. The inspiration for Batman came from various sources, including the pulp magazine heroes of the 1930s and the myth of the bat. The most well - known origin story of Batman is that young Bruce Wayne witnessed the murder of his parents, Thomas and Martha Wayne, in an alley. This traumatic event drove him to vow to fight crime and protect the people of Gotham City.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apple</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/apple.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple" /><published>2025-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/apple</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/apple.html"><![CDATA[<p>An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.</p>

<p>Apple trees are cultivated worldwide, and are the most widely grown
species in the genus Malus. The tree originated in Central Asia, where
its wild ancestor, Malus sieversii, is still found today. Apples have
been grown for thousands of years in Asia and Europe, and were brought
to North America by European colonists.</p>]]></content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kiwifruit</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/kiwifruit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kiwifruit" /><published>2025-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/kiwifruit</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/kiwifruit.html"><![CDATA[<p>Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the
edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.</p>

<p>The most common cultivar group of kiwifruit is oval, about the size of
a large hen’s egg (5–8 cm (2.0–3.1 in) in length and 4.5–5.5 cm
(1.8–2.2 in) in diameter). It has a fibrous, dull greenish-brown skin
and bright green or golden flesh with rows of tiny, black, edible
seeds. The fruit has a soft texture, with a sweet and unique flavor.</p>]]></content><author><name>ted</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bananas</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/23/bananas.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bananas" /><published>2025-04-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/04/23/bananas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/23/bananas.html"><![CDATA[<p>A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several
kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.</p>

<p>In some countries, bananas used for cooking may be called “plantains”,
distinguishing them from dessert bananas. The fruit is variable in size,
color, and firmness, but is usually elongated and curved, with soft
flesh rich in starch covered with a rind, which may be green, yellow,
red, purple, or brown when ripe.</p>]]></content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.]]></summary></entry></feed>